arizonahighways.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy | AZ Highways

### This is the Web site of  _Arizona Highways_  magazine. We are a division of the Arizona Department of Transportation, State of Arizona.

Our postal address is 2039 West Lewis Avenue, Phoenix, AZ 85009. You may contact us by telephone at 602-712-2200, by fax at 602-254-4505, or by e-mail as noted below.

  * [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#096a7c7a7d66646c7b567a6c7b7f606a6c49687b607366676861606e617e68707a2760676f66): subscriptions, changes of address and back issue requests, catalog request, questions regarding catalog products and customer service.
  * [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#97e0f2f5faf6e4e3f2e5d7f6e5feedf8f9f6fffef0ffe0f6eee4b9f4f8fa): link requests, online technical questions or problems.
  * [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5023313c3523103122392a3f3e3138393738273129237e333f3d): corporate and trade sales.

  * **<http://www.azoca.gov/>: The Ombudsman-Citizens Aide helps citizens to resolve ongoing issues with State Agencies.**

Our web server recognizes each visitor's internet provider (IP) address and the action of each person while on our site. We collect aggregate information on those pages persons access or visit. The information we collect is used to measure traffic within our site, improve the content of our Web site and for internal review.

E-mail addresses are collected from those who communicate with us via e-mail, or from customers who purchase subscriptions or products from us online. Your postal address and telephone number are required for catalog purchases. We will telephone you only with questions or information regarding your order.

We may occasionally use e-mail and postal addresses to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and new products and services or upcoming events we think you might find interesting. We may also make our e-mail and postal lists available to other companies and organizations that you may have an interest in. If you do not wish to receive e-mail or mailed marketing materials from us, or you do not want us to share your e-mail or postal address with other organizations, please "Opt Out" when placing your order through our online catalog, or by sending us e-mail.

All online catalog purchase transactions are Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted for your protection. You will be sent e-mail confirming your catalog order. A user name and password will be assigned to you on your order confirmation, which you can retain and use for faster checkout on future catalog orders.

The  _Arizona Highways_  magazine Web site includes links to other sites whose privacy policies we do not control. Once you leave our server, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the site you are visiting.

**EU PRIVACY POLICY — Updated 5/29/18​**

In compliance with the European GDPR Privacy Policy we have updated our policies for EU subscribers and catalog purchasers. By renewing (or subscribing) or purchasing a product from our catalog you consent to Arizona Highways retaining your personal data you have provided, including your name, mailing address and email address. The information provided will be used only for the purpose of managing your subscription, processing renewal fees and payments, delivering your subscription and products, and reminding you of subscription expiration dates. We will not share your information with any third party other than vendors that provide subscription management services for us and that agree to comply with our data privacy policies. You have the right to withdraw your consent that we retain your personal data and information at any time by contacting [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5b382e282f34363e2904283e292d32383e1b3a29322134353a33323c332c3a22287532353d34).
